{
    "id": "482b72b52e7e4616af506743d8b9247d",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met ………………………. pretty girl there.",
            "description": "We use a here because the listener does not know which girl we are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………………. interesting movie.",
            "description": "We use ‘an’ here because the reader /listener does not know which movie we are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. child is playing with his toys.",
            "description": "We use the here because we are talking about a particular child. ",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………….. finest actor I have ever seen.",
            "description": "We use the with superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you see …………………………. cat over there?",
            "description": "Either could be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She wants to be ……………………… architect.",
            "description": "A/an is often used to mean one.",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is …………………………… spider on the roof.",
            "description": "A/an is often used to mean one.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Rich people must help ……………………………….",
            "description": "The poor means all poor people. ",
            "answers": [
                "poor",
                "a poor",
                "the poor"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………………….. mole on her right arm.",
            "description": "A mole means one mole. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. train arrives at",
            "description": "We are talking about a particular train here.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are not feeling well, you should consult ………………………… doctor.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with slightly different meaning. If we use ‘the’ it means that the listener knows which doctor we are talking about. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is seeing …………………………… French girl.",
            "description": "The speaker does not say which French girl they are talking about. Hence, we use 'a' here. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}